好吧，我们今天要改变主题，我们将更多地讨论变分
all right we're changing subject today we're gonna talk more on variational
we're gonna talk more on variational methods but there are some new methods
方法，但有一些新方法
在我从上周四和周二开始从上一个讲座开始之前
we're gonna talk more on variational methods but there are some new methods
before I start the lectures from the last from last Thursday and Tuesday
在我从上周四和周二开始从上一个讲座开始之前
last from last Thursday and Tuesday they're updated there on the web
他们在网上更新了，我花了很多时间来解决
they're updated there on the web it took me lots of times to fix about
it took me lots of times to fix about the 1000 formulas so I hope someone will
1000个公式，所以我希望有人能到达他们，好吧，他们有很多
the 1000 formulas so I hope someone will reach them okay they have a lots of
reach them okay they have a lots of valuable information some things we do
有价值的信息我们没有涉及某些内容，因此请查看全部
valuable information some things we do not cover so please take a look all
not cover so please take a look all right so maybe they because today I'm
对，所以也许是因为今天我要跳到这个特殊的地方
right so maybe they because today I'm gonna be jumping on this particular
gonna be jumping on this particular lecture now I am NOT going to emphasize
现在的演讲中，我不会强调什么的最大目的
lecture now I am NOT going to emphasize the biggest end of what exactly the
the biggest end of what exactly the local variation left to start but I will
还需要开始本地变化，但是我会给您一些新想法
local variation left to start but I will give you some sort of new ideas okay
give you some sort of new ideas okay excuse me a review so we can deviate a
请原谅我，以便我们可以稍微偏离我们所知道的，所以我们
excuse me a review so we can deviate a little bit from what we know so we the
little bit from what we know so we the key ingredient in variational method was
变分法的关键要素是我们有一些数据，我们有一些
key ingredient in variational method was we have some data we have some of the
we have some data we have some of the ativ latent variables with each data
每个数据点都带有ativ潜在变量，我们编写了这一点
ativ latent variables with each data point and we wrote the this is the point
point and we wrote the this is the point fundamental identity the long likelihood
基本身份，长期可能性是下限，失去了距离
fundamental identity the long likelihood being the lower bound lost the distance
being the lower bound lost the distance between Q and P and what is important to
在Q和P之间，要记住的重要一点是
between Q and P and what is important to remember is both the definition of the
remember is both the definition of the lower bound to have the path that
下界具有明显具有Q之间的KL距离的路径
lower bound to have the path that clearly have the KL distance between Q
clearly have the KL distance between Q and P because this distance is not
和P，因为这个距离不是对称的
and P because this distance is not symmetric okay
symmetric okay so Q is the variational approximation of
所以Q是潜在变量后验的变分近似
so Q is the variational approximation of the posterior of the latent variables
the posterior of the latent variables okay P is this distribution and the
好的P是这个分布，下界基本上是期望值
okay P is this distribution and the lower bound basically is the expectation
lower bound basically is the expectation with respect to the validation of
关于此块的分布验证，
with respect to the validation of distribution of this block here that
distribution of this block here that involves the joining of likelihood and
涉及似然性和变异分布的结合，我们有
involves the joining of likelihood and the variation distribution and we have
the variation distribution and we have seen that this is an easy way to to work
看到这是一种简单的工作方式，因为联合对数似然是
seen that this is an easy way to to work with because the joint log likelihood is
with because the joint log likelihood is usually a very
通常一个非常你知道这是一种幻想或
usually a very you know it's an illusion or the
you know it's an illusion or the exponential primal poverty of
指数分布的原始贫困，但如果您必须分析
exponential primal poverty of distributions but if you must analyze
distributions but if you must analyze throughout the distribution you get to
在整个分布中，您将成为高斯混合，例如某些东西
throughout the distribution you get to be a Gaussian mix for example something
be a Gaussian mix for example something that is not computationally easy to work
在计算上不容易使用
that is not computationally easy to work with
with okay so this is the lower bound this is
好的，这是下界，这是我要返回的KL距离
okay so this is the lower bound this is the KL distance I'm going to come back
the KL distance I'm going to come back to this equation shortly but you know in
不久，但您知道在某些方面您还可以考虑
to this equation shortly but you know in some ways you can also consider the
some ways you can also consider the joint log likelihood as being the UH
联合对数似然性是后部正常情况的UH归一化版本
joint log likelihood as being the UH normalized version of the posterior okay
normalized version of the posterior okay so if you see it like this then you can
因此，如果您看到这样的图像，那么您可以立即看到，而我有
so if you see it like this then you can immediately see and I have this for
immediately see and I have this for another slide but you can write this as
另一张幻灯片，但您可以将其写为减去Q与它们之间的KL距离
another slide but you can write this as minus the KL distance between Q and they
minus the KL distance between Q and they are normalized posterior usually you
通常是后验的，通常在文献中看不到，但是我
are normalized posterior usually you don't see that in the literature but I
don't see that in the literature but I think I'm going to make use about in the
认为我要在今天的讲座中充分利用好，所以这
think I'm going to make use about in the lectures today all right okay so this
lectures today all right okay so this methodology basically we apply to lots
方法论基本上，我们适用于很多问题，它附带
methodology basically we apply to lots of problems okay and it comes with
of problems okay and it comes with different names but basically
不同的名称，但基本上是可变的基础是您在
different names but basically variational base is what you see in the
variational base is what you see in the literature so today we're going to try
文学，所以今天我们将尝试介绍一些新方法，其中
literature so today we're going to try to introduce some new methods where
to introduce some new methods where instead of minimizing the distance
而不是最小化Q和P之间的距离或最大化它
instead of minimizing the distance between Q and P or maximizing this we
between Q and P or maximizing this we will try to minimize the opposite KL
将尝试最小化相对的KL距离P和Q之间的距离
will try to minimize the opposite KL distance the distance between P and Q
distance the distance between P and Q you say why not right I mean it's
你说为什么不对，我的意思是那是遥远的，可以接受的距离好吗
you say why not right I mean it's distant and acceptable distance okay you
distant and acceptable distance okay you may argue about that why not
可能会争辩说为什么不最小化P之间的相对距离
may argue about that why not minimize the opposite distance between P
minimize the opposite distance between P and Q some writing this explicitly here
和Q有些人在这里明确写成减去实际后验
and Q some writing this explicitly here as minus the actual posterior and this
as minus the actual posterior and this is the variation on distribution
是分布的变化，很明显，您可以看到这不是
is the variation on distribution obviously you can see that this is not
obviously you can see that this is not an easy integral to calculate because if
易于计算的积分，因为如果您必须基本上采用
an easy integral to calculate because if you have to basically to take the
you have to basically to take the expectations of this with respect to the
关于确切的后孔正确性的期望，这是一个
expectations of this with respect to the exact posterior well right that's a
exact posterior well right that's a mistake here
这里的错误是正确的谢谢你，所以这是
mistake here that's right thank you so this is the
that's right thank you so this is the stone basically here we'll collect this
基本上，这里我们会收集这项权利，因此您必须采取有效措施
stone basically here we'll collect this right so effectively you have to take an
right so effectively you have to take an expectation with extract it with respect
相对于您没有的确切后验将其提取出来的期望
expectation with extract it with respect to the exact posterior which you don't
to the exact posterior which you don't know that's what we need to approximate
知道这就是我们需要近似的值，但是我们将要做一些
know that's what we need to approximate however we're going to do some
however we're going to do some one-stroke a list and we will see that
轻描淡写一个列表，我们将看到它导致了整个类别
one-stroke a list and we will see that it leads to a whole category of
it leads to a whole category of algorithms that they're extremely
在问题速度方面非常受欢迎的算法
algorithms that they're extremely popular in the velocity of problems
popular in the velocity of problems especially in graphs that go the name
特别是在名称期望传播和
especially in graphs that go the name expectation propagation and and very
expectation propagation and and very various variants of love okay so we will
爱情的各种变体好吧，所以我们今天会看到，我想我已经向你展示了
various variants of love okay so we will see that today I think I have shown you
see that today I think I have shown you this trivial example so that you can
这个简单的例子，这样您就可以保持警惕，这有点像
this trivial example so that you can keep your eyes on so this is sort of a
keep your eyes on so this is sort of a distribution that it's a man-made
它是一个人为分布，一些高斯术语，一些
distribution that it's a man-made distribution some gaussian terms some
distribution some gaussian terms some sigmoid thing and we try to approximate
乙状结肠，我们尝试用我们拥有的不同事物来对此进行近似
sigmoid thing and we try to approximate this with different things that we have
this with different things that we have seen up to now in the class so let's say
到目前为止，在课堂上看到的，所以我们说这是实际的分布
seen up to now in the class so let's say this is the actual distribution this
this is the actual distribution this dark region this is the Laplace
黑暗区域，这是我们已经拥有的拉普拉斯近似值
dark region this is the Laplace approximation that we already have
approximation that we already have discussed it center around the mold and
讨论它围绕模具，这是我想这是
discussed it center around the mold and this is I suppose this is the
this is I suppose this is the distribution that you get with
通过最小化
distribution that you get with variational based by minimizing the
variational based by minimizing the distance between Q and P and I'm going
Q和P之间的距离，我将在稍后的文献中向您展示
distance between Q and P and I'm going to show you later on the literature on
to show you later on the literature on the top of this graph the same plot
该图的顶部显示相同的图，但最小化了P之间的距离
the top of this graph the same plot but minimizing the distance between P
but minimizing the distance between P and Q and your set of things looking to
和Q以及您希望有所不同的事物，我将转向
and Q and your set of things looking to be different I'm going to twist to the
be different I'm going to twist to the fundamental problem in variational
变分方法中的基本问题，我们希望最小化距离
fundamental problem in variational methods we want to minimize the distance
methods we want to minimize the distance of Q from P over to maximized right to
Q从P到最大右下角最大化的下限，而我只是
of Q from P over to maximized right to maximize the lower bound and I just
maximize the lower bound and I just mentioned before
前面提到的下限真的没什么
mentioned before that the lower bound is really nothing
that the lower bound is really nothing else but the KL distance between Q and V
否则，将Q和V之间的KL距离归一化为立体声碎片
else but the KL distance between Q and V are normalized for stereo debris does
are normalized for stereo debris does this look to you like the lower bound
在您看来，这就像没有下限的下限，我是那个较低的
this look to you like the lower bound without the minus I is that the lower
without the minus I is that the lower bound
没有-时间的约束，所以我插入一个负号
bound without the - time so I plug in a minus
without the - time so I plug in a minus sign there right you can see that really
在右边签名，您可以看到，这实际上是Q与
sign there right you can see that really this is the distance between Q and
this is the distance between Q and Kelvin EP for curly piece basically in a
卷曲片段的Kelvin EP基本上是针对立体声进行归一化的，所以这仅仅是
Kelvin EP for curly piece basically in a normalize for stereo so this is just
normalize for stereo so this is just another way to look at it but I'm going
另一种看待它的方法，但是如果您进行扩展，我将在这里使用它
another way to look at it but I'm going to make use of this here if you expand
to make use of this here if you expand actually this problem if you basically
其实这个问题，如果你基本上得到了，但这等于距离
actually this problem if you basically get but this is equal to the distance
get but this is equal to the distance between Q and P plus some some constant
在Q和P之间加上组织tau中的一些常数项就可以了
between Q and P plus some some constant term okay in organization tau so
term okay in organization tau so remember that with the lower bound you
请记住，使用下限，您实际上可以自己将其编写为
remember that with the lower bound you can actually itself you can write it as
can actually itself you can write it as as you know as the KL distant and
如您所知，是KL遥远的地方，我将要跳很多
as you know as the KL distant and introduced I'm going to jump a lot of
introduced I'm going to jump a lot of slides since you don't have a copy of
幻灯片，因为您没有幻灯片的副本，这没关系，所以我
slides since you don't have a copy of the slides it doesn't matter so I'm
the slides it doesn't matter so I'm going to go long way down the road all
将会走很长一段路，所以我们将讨论
going to go long way down the road all right so we will discuss
right so we will discuss approximating procedures but in problems
近似的程序，但是在那种图论很厚的问题中，所以我
approximating procedures but in problems that sort of graph theory thick so I'm
that sort of graph theory thick so I'm going to give you a simple setup where
将为您提供一个简单的设置，在这里我们尝试说我们来自
going to give you a simple setup where we try that let's say we are coming from
we try that let's say we are coming from a Gaussian and we want to compute the
高斯，我们想计算高斯的未知均值，我们把
a Gaussian and we want to compute the unknown mean of the Gaussian and we put
unknown mean of the Gaussian and we put some prior on that main stroke basically
主要笔画上的一些先验基本上是后验被写为先验
some prior on that main stroke basically the posterior is written as the prior
the posterior is written as the prior times the likelihood which is looking
乘以看起来像是椭圆形的椭圆形的可能性
times the likelihood which is looking like that so basically rocky elliptic
like that so basically rocky elliptic version of this problem is using a
这个问题的版本使用的是因子图
version of this problem is using a factor graph you have
factor graph you have the fact of knowledge that encodes the
编码先验码的概率的知识事实，然后
the fact of knowledge that encodes the probability of the prior yard and then
probability of the prior yard and then for its likely to tell me have another
因为它可能告诉我还有另一个因素可以将这与
for its likely to tell me have another factor that connects this is a meal with
factor that connects this is a meal with the data X I that you get okay so we
数据XI，您就可以了，所以我们有一些哥谭，这会
the data X I that you get okay so we have something I Gotham and this would
have something I Gotham and this would be fundamental flow problems today when
今天是基本的流量问题，当您尝试在此处估算时，我们将尽力
be fundamental flow problems today when you try to estimate here now we'll try
you try to estimate here now we'll try to approximate this notice that the
近似这个注意点，该示例仍然使用好了，所以
to approximate this notice that the example still utilizes alright so
example still utilizes alright so basically here compensates for prices
基本上是在补偿价格，因为我们一次收集一个数据
basically here compensates for prices because we collect data one at the time
because we collect data one at the time so P of x1 given n P of x2 given M but
所以给定x1的P给定n给定x2的P给定M，但是您几乎可以在每个证明的BC中考虑
so P of x1 given n P of x2 given M but you can think almost in every proven BC
you can think almost in every proven BC graphical model thing there is a
图形模型的东西有因式分解，所以在有向图中
graphical model thing there is a factorization so in in directed graphs
factorization so in in directed graphs maybe we fertilized on the probability
也许我们受精于节点给定父母在您的概率
maybe we fertilized on the probability of the nodes given their parents in you
of the nodes given their parents in you know in undirected graphs we factorize
知道在无向图中我们将潜在的服务器连接分解
know in undirected graphs we factorize as potential server connected
as potential server connected specification and at least now can we
规范，至少现在我们可以真正想出一种方法
specification and at least now can we actually figure out a way to come up
actually figure out a way to come up with some approximation of this
以某种方式模仿此后代
with some approximation of this posteriors in a way that somehow mimics
posteriors in a way that somehow mimics this factorization right obviously if
如果确切的分布看起来像这样，那么分解显然是正确的
this factorization right obviously if the exact distribution looks like that
the exact distribution looks like that maybe it only makes sense to have some
也许只有这种变异才能有意义
maybe it only makes sense to have some in this factorization for the variation
in this factorization for the variation of distribution so this is what we're
分布，这就是我们今天要尝试利用的
of distribution so this is what we're going to try to take advantage today
going to try to take advantage today okay telling me it will issue an example
好吧，告诉我它将发布一个示例，稍后我们将再次与之一起使用
okay telling me it will issue an example which we will play with later this again
which we will play with later this again estimating the mean of the distribution
估计分布的均值，所以我们从高斯抽样，这是
estimating the mean of the distribution so we sample from a Gaussian this is the
so we sample from a Gaussian this is the Gaussian but actually we the actual
高斯，但实际上我们要显示要计算的实际分布
Gaussian but actually we the actual distribution we show we want to compute
distribution we show we want to compute this mean theta like in the previous
这意味着像上一个问题中的theta，但实际上是分布
this mean theta like in the previous problem but actually the distribution we
problem but actually the distribution we sample is not just clean Gaussian but
样本不仅是干净的高斯，还包括一些高斯
sample is not just clean Gaussian but this Gaussian plus some
this Gaussian plus some all right so this is what's called the
好的，这就是所谓的拍手问题，所以如果你能想到的话
all right so this is what's called the clattering problem so if you can think
clattering problem so if you can think of you having this Gaussian you really
你们中有这个高斯的人，您真的想升级这场雨，但是
of you having this Gaussian you really want to escalate this rain but the
want to escalate this rain but the samples you get are basically either
您获得的样本基本上要么来自实际的高斯
samples you get are basically either going to come from the actual Gaussian
going to come from the actual Gaussian what we're going to just noise he went
我们将要去噪音的是他去估计参数theta
what we're going to just noise he went to the estimation of the parameter theta
to the estimation of the parameter theta so in this problem ranges to compute the
所以在这个问题范围内计算一阶基本上是
so in this problem ranges to compute the first order is basically the
first order is basically the unnormalized posterior as the prior
未归一化的后验作为活动的可能性和H的先前时间
unnormalized posterior as the prior times the likelihood and H of an active
times the likelihood and H of an active in terms is a Gaussian mixture so if you
用高斯混合表示，所以如果您有n个数据点，并且将其扩展
in terms is a Gaussian mixture so if you have n data points and you expand this
have n data points and you expand this product there you're going to get 2 to
那里的乘积将得到2的N，所以状态可以非常
product there you're going to get 2 to the N so the state can be very
the N so the state can be very complicated okay so can we actually do
复杂，好吧，我们可以实际使用变分方法吗
complicated okay so can we actually do with variational methods in a way that
with variational methods in a way that this is computationally easy to work
这在计算上很容易使用
this is computationally easy to work with
with okay so we will discuss this problem
好吧，我们今天将讨论这个问题
okay so we will discuss this problem today which fella is like okay this has
today which fella is like okay this has lots of substance and I think what's
很多实质内容，我认为这可能是唯一的理论幻灯片
lots of substance and I think what's probably the only theoretical slide in
probably the only theoretical slide in the North today
北方今天停止尝试关注我们删除
the North today stop trying to pay attention we remove
stop trying to pay attention we remove the skin or everything we're going to do
皮肤或我们今天将要做的所有事情，我们使用的近似值可以是
the skin or everything we're going to do today approximations we using can be the
today approximations we using can be the whole distribution or maybe some factor
整个分布或我们可能要近似的一些因素
whole distribution or maybe some factor in the approximation we're going to
in the approximation we're going to assume that those factors are coming
假设这些因素来自指数族，因此在此
assume that those factors are coming from the exponential family so in this
from the exponential family so in this particular case I write the distribution
在特殊情况下，我给定一些自然参数，写出G的分布Q
particular case I write the distribution Q of G given some natural parameters
Q of G given some natural parameters theta in the generic form of the
Z的指数形式分布G的一般形式的theta
theta in the generic form of the exponential form distributions G of Z of
exponential form distributions G of Z of the sufficient statistics and the rest
足够的统计信息，其余的基本上您都知道一些归一化
the sufficient statistics and the rest of basically you know some normalization
of basically you know some normalization term and H of Z term Vista is the form
术语和Z术语的H术语Vista是我们用于指数族的形式
term and H of Z term Vista is the form we used for the exponential family okay
we used for the exponential family okay a lot includes a lot of different
很多包括很多不同的分布
a lot includes a lot of different distributions
distributions all right so let's go to the new problem
好吧，让我们来看一个新的问题，那就是最小化
all right so let's go to the new problem which is the minimization of the
which is the minimization of the distance from the actual distribution P
与实际分布P和各种分布Q之间的距离
distance from the actual distribution P and the various distribution Q but here
and the various distribution Q but here we assume that fewest experience a
我们假设经历家庭分布的人最少，所以请记住情况
we assume that fewest experience a family distribution so remember the case
family distribution so remember the case distance is minus P that can repeat all
距离是负数P，可以重复一次，所以这是怎么回事，所以我有
distance is minus P that can repeat all right so what is this coming so I have
right so what is this coming so I have to calculate this you have to take - the
要计算这一点，您必须采取-对P或
to calculate this you have to take - the expectations with respect to P or the
expectations with respect to P or the norm of K over V right and not pay the
K超过V的范数，并且基本上不为此P付分母
norm of K over V right and not pay the denominator basically with this P will
denominator basically with this P will give me a constant because it doesn't
给我一个常数，因为它不依赖于Q，所以我要保持警惕
give me a constant because it doesn't depend on Q so I'm going to get my nose
depend on Q so I'm going to get my nose the expression of the love of this so
爱的表达，所以，我们正在研究所有的术语，
the expression of the love of this so and we're looking at all the terms that
and we're looking at all the terms that depend you know here on Z and ether so
取决于您对Z和以太的了解，因此我们将减去Z和的对数
depend you know here on Z and ether so we're going to have minus log of Z and
we're going to have minus log of Z and the exponential will give me e 2
指数将给我e 2换位，期望为
the exponential will give me e 2 transpose and the expectation with
transpose and the expectation with respect to P of Z that's the exact
关于Z的P，这就是您的确切分布，我们同意
respect to P of Z that's the exact distribution of you see we agree that
distribution of you see we agree that this is basically the kale this one's a
这基本上是羽衣甘蓝，使用该视图的人很多
this is basically the kale this one's a lot using that view
再次在影片距离中有一个减号，所以-成为全局队列
right again in the film distance there's a minus sign so - be a global queue
a minus sign so - be a global queue avert this or you're going to get minus
避免这种情况，否则您将减去脚本撒尿的期望
avert this or you're going to get minus the expectation of the scripted to pee
the expectation of the scripted to pee or belongeth - all right so we take
或beforeeth-好的，所以我们将全局队列期望值减去
or belongeth - all right so we take global queue expectation with a minus
global queue expectation with a minus sign you get that okay so we want to
迹象表明您没问题，所以我们想找到最小化的参数theta
sign you get that okay so we want to find the parameters theta that minimizes
find the parameters theta that minimizes this - reverse camber verbs and so
这-反向弯度动词，所以您将带导数
this - reverse camber verbs and so you're going to take the derivative with
you're going to take the derivative with respect to it and you're going to set
尊重它，你将把它们设置为零，所以你要
respect to it and you're going to set them equal to zero so you're going to
them equal to zero so you're going to have the gradient of this term with
具有相对于e theta的该项的梯度，所以这是龙
have the gradient of this term with respect to e theta so this is dragon
respect to e theta so this is dragon again respect to theta and this will
再次尊重theta，这将使您对Z的U的期望与
again respect to theta and this will give you the expectation of U of Z with
give you the expectation of U of Z with respect to P of Z and object forgot to
关于Z的P和对象忘了把T的U的期望放在这里
respect to P of Z and object forgot to put here the expectation of U of T okay
put here the expectation of U of T okay so actually equate this equation here
所以实际上等式在这里看起来应该不像这样
so actually equate this equation here should look like no actually this is
should look like no actually this is something different
有所不同，所以在这里我们必须将U的括号放在
something different so here we have to put brackets of U of
so here we have to put brackets of U of Z okay the calculation of theta is start
好的，theta的计算是从最佳ETA开始的，
Z okay the calculation of theta is start out the optimal ETA is such that the
out the optimal ETA is such that the gradient - the gradient of the love of G
梯度-G的爱的梯度是U相对于E的期望
gradient - the gradient of the love of G is the expectation of U with respect to
is the expectation of U with respect to the exact B of Z and the exactly of Z of
Z的确切B和Z的确切当然不知道，我也不会
the exact B of Z and the exactly of Z of course is not know and I'm not going to
course is not know and I'm not going to prove it
证明一下，你可以看看最后的笔记
prove it you can look at the notes from last
you can look at the notes from last semester you can go to Wikipedia for
一个学期，您可以去维基百科获取指数级的家庭分布
semester you can go to Wikipedia for exponential family distributions you
exponential family distributions you include is an exponential family
include是可以显示任何Q in的指数族分布
include is an exponential family distribution you can show for any Q in
distribution you can show for any Q in this family that - the gradient of the
这个家庭，-G的对数的梯度是对
this family that - the gradient of the log of G is the expectation of the
log of G is the expectation of the sufficient statistics with respect to
有关G键的足够统计信息
sufficient statistics with respect to key of G
key of G anybody knows
任何人都知道
组合实际上是一行，所以对于任何地区都没有
key of G anybody knows
the combination is literally one line okay so for any district there's no
组合实际上是一行，所以对于任何地区都没有
okay so for any district there's no approximation here if I have
如果我有指数喜剧的分布，则为此处的近似值
approximation here if I have distribution from the exponential comedy
distribution from the exponential comedy and you take the expectation of the
并且您期望获得有关Q的足够统计信息
and you take the expectation of the sufficient statistics with respect to Q
sufficient statistics with respect to Q alright this comes to me minus the
好吧，这给我减去了G的对数的梯度，您可以
alright this comes to me minus the gradient of the log of G and you can
gradient of the log of G and you can extend this actually to higher
实际上，您也可以将其扩展到更高的导数
extend this actually to higher derivatives as well you know for
derivatives as well you know for calculating all the moments for any
从指数计算任何分布的所有矩
calculating all the moments for any distribution from the exponential
distribution from the exponential probability and this is an identity that
概率，这是我们通过最小化此逆向计算得出的恒等式
probability and this is an identity that we computed by minimizing this reversed
we computed by minimizing this reversed km diversity okay this is a problem we
公里的多样性好吧，这是一个问题，我们想找到所有问题，以便我们
km diversity okay this is a problem we want to find all right so that we
want to find all right so that we minimize the diversity elevator so you
最小化分集提升器，因此您可以看到这是对数的对数负梯度
minimize the diversity elevator so you can see this is minus gradient of log of
can see this is minus gradient of log of G minus gradient of G so you can put
G减去G的斜率，因此您可以将Z的期望透视图P设为
G minus gradient of G so you can put this expectation perspective P of Z of
this expectation perspective P of Z of the uz the term that was here all right
uz这个在这里可以等于Z的U期望的术语
the uz the term that was here all right equal to the expectation of U of Z with
equal to the expectation of U of Z with respect to Q of Z and then you get this
相对于Z的Q，然后您在这里得到一个很好的标识，这是我们最终的
respect to Q of Z and then you get this nice identity here which is our final
nice identity here which is our final result and that result says that the
结果，该结果表明Z的U的期望相对于
result and that result says that the expectation of U of Z with respect to
expectation of U of Z with respect to the approximate distribution is the same
近似分布与Z的U的期望相同
the approximate distribution is the same as the expectation of U of Z with
as the expectation of U of Z with respect to the exact distribution and
尊重确切的分布，显然您可以进一步推广它，
respect to the exact distribution and obviously you can push it further and
obviously you can push it further and you use second order moment you can
您可以使用二阶矩来解决Z的变体
you use second order moment you can solve at the variant of your Z with
solve at the variant of your Z with respect to Q of Z equal to the variance
相对于Z的Q等于Y或Z相对于Z的P的方差等
respect to Q of Z equal to the variance of Y or Z with respect to P of Z etc etc
of Y or Z with respect to P of Z etc etc so the conclusion is that when you try
因此得出的结论是，当您尝试最小化照护时，它们会从
so the conclusion is that when you try to minimize the care they start from a
to minimize the care they start from a distribution P from another distribution
指数族中另一个分布Q的分布P可以
distribution P from another distribution Q in the exponential family all right
Q in the exponential family all right then
那么P和Q的时刻一定可以，所以
then the moments of P and Q must okay so the
the moments of P and Q must okay so the distribution is P and Q have the same
分布是P和Q现在拥有相同的办公室，如果您可以这样说的话
distribution is P and Q have the same office now if you may say so does not
office now if you may say so does not mean that because the moments of an
意味着因为指数分布的矩真正定义了
mean that because the moments of an exponential distribution really define
exponential distribution really define the distribution
分布，但是B是
the distribution but B is an exponential distribution of
but B is an exponential distribution of the various we're going to approximate
与家人打交道的各种事情，我们都会与您近似
the various we're going to approximate to you whatever pierced with the family
to you whatever pierced with the family from the exponential distribution but we
从指数分布来看，但我们知道家庭将会变得如此
from the exponential distribution but we know that family is going to be such
know that family is going to be such that the moments of the sufficient
足够的统计数据的时刻我们必须绘制时刻图
that the moments of the sufficient statistics we have to map the moments
statistics we have to map the moments that we get with respect to the exact
我们关于C的确切分布P得到的这就是为什么
that we get with respect to the exact distribution P of C now that's why you
distribution P of C now that's why you will see this in the literature
会在文学作品中看到这一点，有时人们称此刻
will see this in the literature sometimes people call this moment
sometimes people call this moment matching okay
匹配，好吧，我们必须从我们所拥有的东西中正确
matching okay we must be correct from what we have
we must be correct from what we have seen in afternoon support if you may
在下午的支持中看到，如果您可以保持安全，因为这是指数部分
seen in afternoon support if you may keep safe because this exponential part
keep safe because this exponential part need to be a Gaussian right and you
需要成为高斯的权利，而您试图说服高斯
need to be a Gaussian right and you trying to persuade with a Gaussian with
trying to persuade with a Gaussian with a Gaussian any distribution P of Z then
高斯的Z的任意分布P，然后惊讶地发现Neil必须是
a Gaussian any distribution P of Z then then get surprised that Neil has to be
then get surprised that Neil has to be the mean of P of Z and that Sigma has to
Z的P的均值和Sigma必须是Z的P的方差
the mean of P of Z and that Sigma has to be the variance of P of Z in a remind
be the variance of P of Z in a remind you sample actually in the earlier notes
您可以在前面的笔记中实际采样，很快就可以进行正确的授课
you sample actually in the earlier notes very quickly lectures to go with right
very quickly lectures to go with right approximate the distribution P with a
用高斯近似分布P，我想让你回去
approximate the distribution P with a Gaussian and I want you to go back and
Gaussian and I want you to go back and see when we minimize the distance of Q
看到当我们最小化Q与P的距离而不是P与Q的距离时，我们实际上会得到
see when we minimize the distance of Q from P not P from Q we will actually get
from P not P from Q we will actually get this result we got something else
如果我们将距离最小化，我们会得到其他结果
this result we got something else you know if we minimize the distance of
you know if we minimize the distance of P until me and the moon will have to be
P，直到我和月亮都必须成为Till的中庸之物
P until me and the moon will have to be the mean of Till's
the mean of Till's you know of P of Z and the signal have
您知道Z的P，并且信号必须是美丽的方差，所以改变了
you know of P of Z and the signal have to be the variance of beauty so changed
to be the variance of beauty so changed for example if you try to compute some
例如，如果您尝试计算一些参数，则可以知道
for example if you try to compute some parameters you know take the mean of the
parameters you know take the mean of the Gaussian right and this is the dark blue
高斯权，这是深蓝色，是确切的分布，所以当您
Gaussian right and this is the dark blue is the exact distribution so when you
is the exact distribution so when you minimized with normal matching you will
通过正常匹配最小化，您将获得高斯分布，但基本上看起来像
minimized with normal matching you will get a Gaussian but basically looks like
get a Gaussian but basically looks like that okay so you get this with normal
好的，所以您可以正常使用
that okay so you get this with normal much
much five let's make things are more
五个让我们让事情变得更困难的不是设计，而是您自己
five let's make things are more difficult not by design but just you
difficult not by design but just you know like difficult things to be done
睡前知道做困难的事情的家伙，所以我们要
know like difficult things to be done guys before to sleep so we're going to
guys before to sleep so we're going to apply this idea moment watching
基本上立即应用这个想法，然后想出一种新方法
apply this idea moment watching basically and come up with a new method
basically and come up with a new method a very powerful method for doing
在图上进行推理的一种非常强大的方法，称为
a very powerful method for doing inference in graph which is called
inference in graph which is called expectation propagation and you can make
期望传播，您可以设想一下这个词是什么
expectation propagation and you can make this out envisioning what what the word
this out envisioning what what the word expectation propagation means the same
期望传播的含义与我们在图形中传递消息的方式相同
expectation propagation means the same way we did message passing in graphs
way we did message passing in graphs right the idea here that you see that
正确的想法是，您看到预期的财富也许是我们传递的
right the idea here that you see that wealth expectation maybe what we pass in
wealth expectation maybe what we pass in the graph for moment right because the
该图暂时正确，因为我们将以某种方式进行本地操作
the graph for moment right because the local operation somehow we are going to
local operation somehow we are going to be doing would be minimization of some
要做的就是最小化某些变分指数族
be doing would be minimization of some variational exponential family
variational exponential family distribution ki Q so we would passing
分布ki Q，所以我们会经过片刻，这就是为什么地图被称为
distribution ki Q so we would passing moments and that's why the map is called
moments and that's why the map is called expectation propagation so we you know
期望传播，所以我们知道这是我们收集的一些数据
expectation propagation so we you know this is the data we collected some
this is the data we collected some unknown parameter I'm going to do a
未知参数，我将使用这种类型的其他版本
unknown parameter I'm going to do a different versions of this type of
different versions of this type of problems it's introducing sort of
问题，它引入了各种不同的算法，但现在
problems it's introducing sort of different algorithms but right now in a
different algorithms but right now in a typical interest problem equal update of
典型的利益问题等于我们的米theta防御的更新，所以这
typical interest problem equal update of the defense of our meters theta so this
the defense of our meters theta so this is basically Joint Distribution like
基本上是联合分配，例如第一项或零
is basically Joint Distribution like that maybe the first term or the zero
that maybe the first term or the zero term you can make the prior and all the
术语，您可以将先前的术语和所有其他术语设为可能的术语，这样
term you can make the prior and all the other terms to likely to terms okay so
other terms to likely to terms okay so the idea here is we're going to assume
这里的想法是，我们将基本上假设这种可能性
the idea here is we're going to assume basically that this likelihood temps for
basically that this likelihood temps for example okay they're easy to work
例子好吧，他们很容易进行高斯分布
example okay they're easy to work distribution of gaussians right that's
distribution of gaussians right that's the whole idea of approximating
用高斯近似某物的整个想法不是
the whole idea of approximating something with a Gaussian is it's not
something with a Gaussian is it's not Gaussian start with so the exact
高斯开始于，因此确切的后验像这样的超过P的
Gaussian start with so the exact posterior looks like this one over P of
posterior looks like this one over P of D times these factors and again I have
D倍于这些因素，我在这里再次合并了优先部分
D times these factors and again I have incorporated here the prioritized part
incorporated here the prioritized part of themselves so remember that we're
他们自己，所以请记住，我们将使用第一个术语
of themselves so remember that we're going to be using that the first term in
going to be using that the first term in the consolidation especially the prior
合并，特别是之前的其余部分
the consolidation especially the prior the rest of the
the rest of the like adults this is the the
像大人一样，这是正常化的时间，好的，我看这个
like adults this is the the normalization time okay I look at this
normalization time okay I look at this equation and we're gonna say well if you
等式，如果您知道我们将要找到的近似值，我们会说的很好
equation and we're gonna say well if you know what we're gonna find approximate
know what we're gonna find approximate this with some various turn distribution
这个有一些不同的转弯分布，我们将利用这个
this with some various turn distribution we shall take advantage of this
we shall take advantage of this polarization and maybe postulate some
极化并且可能假设θ的一些变化分布，但是
polarization and maybe postulate some variation distribution of theta but
variation distribution of theta but there's a similar factorization
有类似的因式分解好吧，也许兴趣不大
there's a similar factorization okay maybe not significant interest
okay maybe not significant interest because this is an easy problem you
因为这是一个简单的问题，您会注意到，当我问您这个问题时
because this is an easy problem you notice that when I ask you this
notice that when I ask you this polarization each of these factors
这些因素中的每一个都取决于所有相同的量θ，所以
polarization each of these factors depends all the same amount theta so
depends all the same amount theta so this is where a classical Bayesian
这是经典贝叶斯推理问题的所在，因此您可以考虑
this is where a classical Bayesian inference problem so you can think if
inference problem so you can think if you know you have various type of
你知道你有各种类型的参数主要我坚持你知道这些
you know you have various type of parameters main I insist you know these
parameters main I insist you know these are the filters so with the care depends
是过滤器，因此请谨慎使用theta，好的，我们稍后会看到，但是
are the filters so with the care depends on theta okay we will see later but
on theta okay we will see later but maybe have an appreciation for these
也许对这些因素有所了解，然后涉及相同的未知数
maybe have an appreciation for these factors then involve the same unknowns
factors then involve the same unknowns theta but right now that's what we have
theta，但现在我们可以了，所以我们使这种分布永久存在
theta but right now that's what we have okay so we perpetuate this distribution
okay so we perpetuate this distribution that this computation intractable will
这个难以处理的计算是近似值，您能给我通行证吗
that this computation intractable will is approximation can you give me a pass
is approximation can you give me a pass on this is possible algorithm you may
在这可能的算法上，您可能会想出一个近似值
on this is possible algorithm you may come up with you know to approximate
come up with you know to approximate this without I mean just tell me
这不是我的意思，就是告诉我一切，如果这可能
this without I mean just tell me everything that this potentially if this
everything that this potentially if this blogger
博主
当您尝试做某事时，我要说的是最明显的一句话
everything that this potentially if this blogger
I'm going to the most obvious thing someone to say when you try to
当您尝试做某事时，我要说的是最明显的一句话
someone to say when you try to participate this without I mean so for
参加这个活动，我的意思不是，例如，您可以在这里思考，如果您
participate this without I mean so for example you can think here right if you
example you can think here right if you collect data 1 data at the time so maybe
一次收集数据1个数据，所以有人可能会说哦，你知道
collect data 1 data at the time so maybe one comes somebody may say oh you know
one comes somebody may say oh you know I'm going to go and do an approximation
我要去做一个近似的第五人，所以我要
I'm going to go and do an approximation fifth one they took on so I'm going to
fifth one they took on so I'm going to go and do an approximation of her too
去也跟她做个近似
我们能否大致估算出它的流行与否独立于
fifth one they took on so I'm going to go and do an approximation of her too
can we approximate basically it's popular independently of the over the
我们能否大致估算出它的流行与否独立于
popular independently of the over the thing it will work is right but the
它会工作的事情是对的，但重点不是要使其个性化
thing it will work is right but the emphasis is not to make its individual
emphasis is not to make its individual heart firm well the objective is to
坚定不移的目标是很好地近似整个事物，因此
heart firm well the objective is to approximate this whole thing well so the
approximate this whole thing well so the factors individually maybe are good who
个别因素也许是个好人，因为他们会失去目的
factors individually maybe are good who cares because the purpose will be lost
cares because the purpose will be lost okay so for example let's consider I
好吧，例如，让我们考虑一下，我认为这是我是否
okay so for example let's consider I think this this I don't whether this
think this this I don't whether this pictorial comes but let's consider an
图片来了，但让我们考虑一个确切的分布，第一个是
pictorial comes but let's consider an exact distribution the first one is a
exact distribution the first one is a mixture of two thousands
两千个混合的，就是f 1，我们说
mixture of two thousands okay that's f 1 and let's say we're
okay that's f 1 and let's say we're going to approximate this factor with
将与这个失踪的人近似这个因素，因为
going to approximate this factor with this missing person because just to be
this missing person because just to be in the exponential family now she'll so
现在在指数家庭中，她将使两个的第二个因子看起来像
in the exponential family now she'll so the second factor of two looks like a
the second factor of two looks like a Gaussian so we get an extra
高斯，所以我们得到一个额外的近似值，所以如果你采取
Gaussian so we get an extra approximation all right so if you take
approximation all right so if you take so this is the just product of F 1 and F
所以这是F 1和F 2的乘积，这正是我们想要的
so this is the just product of F 1 and F 2 this is really what we want
2 this is really what we want approximate well and now this is the
近似好，现在这是两个近似值的乘积
approximate well and now this is the product of the two approximation and
product of the two approximation and your faith is not a very good
您的信心不是一个很好的计算方法，因为主要是我们将其固定
your faith is not a very good calculation because mainly we screw it
calculation because mainly we screw it up there okay all right we don't know
在那里，好吧，我们不知道你怎么会告诉我你得到了这个
up there okay all right we don't know how you're gonna tell me you get this
how you're gonna tell me you get this model approximation of needs to be very
需求的模型近似值非常好，所以当您
model approximation of needs to be very good so the addition is when you
good so the addition is when you approximate that one right
近似他所放的一项权利，也很有可能
approximate that one right he put and also a lot of probability
he put and also a lot of probability mass in the approximation to match that
近似匹配的质量，但您确实忘记了
mass in the approximation to match that one but you really have forgot that the
one but you really have forgot that the probability mass effective here is zero
此处质量有效的概率为零，因此就像您要投入很多钱一样
probability mass effective here is zero so like you're investing a lot of money
so like you're investing a lot of money to approximate well at one in a region
在一个不存在的区域中近似于一个
to approximate well at one in a region that doesn't
您必须要做的是，我们不采取任何措施使这些因素
you have to do in the we don't approach to make these factors in the penny of
to make these factors in the penny of each other but so we try to to do
彼此，但是我们尝试做得比那更好，所以我只是
each other but so we try to to do something better than that so I just
something better than that so I just have an idea verse for this algorithm
对于这种算法有一个想法的诗句，它也不是很复杂，但是
have an idea verse for this algorithm and again it is not very complicated but
and again it is not very complicated but you need to pay attention the algebra
您需要注意您知道的代数可能会有些混乱
you need to pay attention the algebra you know may be a little bit confusing
you know may be a little bit confusing it is really not okay so I'm going to
真的不行，所以我只做Z，我提醒你
it is really not okay so I'm going to make only the Z and I remind you this
make only the Z and I remind you this kind of thing because the approximation
之类的东西，因为如果您选择近似值，则近似值分布
kind of thing because the approximation the approximate distribution if you pick
the approximate distribution if you pick up so this is part of J so we because we
向上，所以这是J的一部分，所以我们因为我们现在不会像在
up so this is part of J so we because we won't approximate now right like in the
won't approximate now right like in the approximation so okay to be close to
近似值，可以接近这个FJ，我们将尝试使
approximation so okay to be close to this F J we're going to try to make
this F J we're going to try to make distribution as close as possible to the
该漫画作品集验证了与pj x尽可能接近的分布
distribution as close as possible to the pj x this manga folio verifies for the
pj x this manga folio verifies for the surprise of the approximate apart so
当我们计算出126到
surprise of the approximate apart so again when we compute that 126 to coming
again when we compute that 126 to coming it's coming here so we're going to be
它来了，所以我们要近似一些
it's coming here so we're going to be approximating alright
approximating alright this whole distribution to be as close
整个分布要尽可能的好
this whole distribution to be as close as possible to that all right well this
as possible to that all right well this is the exact factor all right but this
是完全正确的因子，但这是我们使用的近似值
is the exact factor all right but this is we use the approximation of for the
is we use the approximation of for the other factors that we have gained up to
到现在为止，我们已经获得了其他因素，我们将继续这样做
other factors that we have gained up to now again we're gonna do this
now again we're gonna do this iteratively right so whatever particles
迭代是正确的，所以无论我们对内部其他粒子有什么粒子
iteratively right so whatever particles we have toward the others within
we have toward the others within approximation so this is what we use as
近似值，这就是我们用作背景的方式
approximation so this is what we use as the background okay
the background okay the first we will be have an
首先，我们将得到j的近似值
the first we will be have an approximation for that j that is
approximation for that j that is accurate in regions where very
准确的地区
如果他们是0，那么大的可能性就向右走，谁在乎我们不会
approximation for that j that is accurate in regions where very
significant probability marched right if they're 0 who cares we are not going to
如果他们是0，那么大的可能性就向右走，谁在乎我们不会
they're 0 who cares we are not going to count for them we don't want to to
为他们计数，我们不想从其他地方投资资源
count for them we don't want to to invest resources from other proximity to
invest resources from other proximity to you say on the bus was here you know we
你说在公共汽车上是在这里，你知道我们有这种棕色的产品
you say on the bus was here you know we have this product of the brown
have this product of the brown distributions all but the term tray so
除了术语托盘以外的所有分布，所以我要定义更长的时间
distributions all but the term tray so longer this i am going to define this
longer this i am going to define this amount to ask you for the key factors
要求您提供除j以外的其他关键因素的有效技巧
amount to ask you for the key factors except total j so effectively the skill
except total j so effectively the skill theta divided by this approximation fo j
θ除以这个近似值，好吧，物理学中的这个机会带有一个
theta divided by this approximation fo j okay this chance in physics comes with a
okay this chance in physics comes with a particular name alright because even
可以使用特定的名称，因为即使这个想法也来自物理学，但是我们
particular name alright because even this idea comes from physics but we
this idea comes from physics but we leave everything out so this is another
遗漏一切，这是牧师的产品的另一个因素
leave everything out so this is another factor the product from the pastors
factor the product from the pastors Bugsy okay all right
越野车好吧好吧
对我来说，这种分布在Q减去J的时候是自然的
factor the product from the pastors Bugsy okay all right
to me this distribution here as natural at a times this distribution Q minus J
对我来说，这种分布在Q减去J的时候是自然的
at a times this distribution Q minus J okay and situation is a normalization
好的，情况是一个归一化因子，所以Z Jake这是最终的
okay and situation is a normalization factor okay so Z Jake here's the final
factor okay so Z Jake here's the final icon alright so what we noticed we want
图标好了，所以我们注意到我们想使此效果尽可能接近
icon alright so what we noticed we want to make this alright as close as
to make this alright as close as possible to dock so here is the problem
可能会停靠，所以这是我们要查找更新的问题
possible to dock so here is the problem we want to find an update of the
we want to find an update of the distribution Q and notice I am NOT
分布Q，请注意，我不是在要求更新J的因子
distribution Q and notice I am NOT asking an update of the factor at J of
asking an update of the factor at J of theta where the next thing is an update
Theta接下来的事情是整个论文队列的更新
theta where the next thing is an update of the whole queue of paper
让我们同意今天活跃起来，但我提出的问题不是为了可爱，是的
let's agree to make the active today but I'm posing the problem not for cute yeah
I'm posing the problem not for cute yeah we're going to take this faster if they
如果他们填满了，我们将以更快的速度处理，但我在摆姿势
we're going to take this faster if they filled up right but I'm posing the
filled up right but I'm posing the problem find me this ablative clear
问题找到我这个烧蚀的透明纸，以便与之匹配，所以
problem find me this ablative clear paper so that it matches that okay so
paper so that it matches that okay so the problem is fine cupid i'd like orvis
问题是丘比特好，我想要orvis q nu theta，以便两者之间的距离
the problem is fine cupid i'd like orvis q nu theta so that the distance between
q nu theta so that the distance between this and this is me might and you notice
这就是我可能的，您会注意到这个很好的缩放距离，因为
this and this is me might and you notice this very well scale distance because
this very well scale distance because the two popular FJ comes to the left
两位受欢迎的FJ都向左进攻，这很重要，所以
the two popular FJ comes to the left attack this very important all right so
attack this very important all right so it's what we discussed today alright so
这就是我们今天讨论的内容，所以这是通过因素，好吧，这
it's what we discussed today alright so this is the through factor okay this
this is the through factor okay this problem is can you tell me with words
问题是你能不能用言语告诉我他们说的是什么人
problem is can you tell me with words they say what is the distribution people
they say what is the distribution people all right that does solve this
确实可以解决此最小化问题，我们当然是
all right that does solve this minimization problem and of course we're
minimization problem and of course we're going to constrain theta theta is in the
要限制theta theta在指数族中，所以
going to constrain theta theta is in the exponential family so the problem of
exponential family so the problem of exponential distribution which is an
指数分布是一种指数形式的分布渠道
exponential distribution which is an exponential form a distribution channel
exponential form a distribution channel exact answer to this problem that is
这个问题的确切答案基本上是从优化中得出的
exact answer to this problem that is basically coming out of the optimization
一直很热
it stays hot right
当我们在观看时，基本上Flippa的治疗时刻必须前进
when we're watching so basically the moments of cure Flippa have to march
moments of cure Flippa have to march through the moments to go okay all right
经过一会儿好吧好吧，所以我们首先说它是高斯
through the moments to go okay all right so let's say it first is Gaussian is
so let's say it first is Gaussian is like I'm going to live with the mean
就像我要习惯于实践中使用的平均语言一样
like I'm going to live with the mean ology used in practice right like taking
ology used in practice right like taking the distribution on the left hand side
在左侧的分布并将其投影到高斯说一些
the distribution on the left hand side and projecting it to Gaussian say some
and projecting it to Gaussian say some  to be the ocean and we're studying
变成海洋，我们正在向附属的高斯研究那些时刻
to be the ocean and we're studying those moments to an affiliated Gaussian
those moments to an affiliated Gaussian okay an operation this can you achieve
好吧，这可以实现文献中写的操作吗？
okay an operation this can you achieve written in the literature there's a
written in the literature there's a projection operator so think of this you
投影运算符，因此，请考虑一下您所拥有的分布
projection operator so think of this you know whatever distribution you have
know whatever distribution you have you're going to approach range with a
您将通过这一步与高斯人接近范围
you're going to approach range with a Gaussian through this one with marching
Gaussian through this one with marching and so you've trapped the moment and
因此，您已经捕捉到了这一刻，然后将它们分配给高斯，因此
and so you've trapped the moment and then you assign them to a Gaussian so
then you assign them to a Gaussian so that's the projections that we computed
那就是我们计算theta的新分布Q的投影，然后我们
that's the projections that we computed new distribution Q of theta and then we
new distribution Q of theta and then we want to update the software at J and I
想要更新J处的软件，并提醒您，C的任务P是
want to update the software at J and I remind you that this mission P of C is
remind you that this mission P of C is written as left J times this
写成左J倍
近似因子，所以theta的XA基本上是
remind you that this mission P of C is written as left J times this
approximation factors so basically XA of theta would be some
近似因子，所以theta的XA基本上是
so basically XA of theta would be some normalization factor that you need times
您需要的归一化因子乘以您的归一化分布Q
normalization factor that you need times a normalized distribution Q that you
a normalized distribution Q that you compute for this problem you should not
计算此问题，您不应该因为需要更新而知道
compute for this problem you should not because one need to update know that the
because one need to update know that the update of the fact of J so addition is
J事实的更新，因此加法近似为theta的整个链
update of the fact of J so addition is approximate the whole chain of theta
approximate the whole chain of theta okay
好吧，另外一个可以做更多
okay and another one that is done with more
and another one that is done with more and matching if we divide it by the
如果我们将其除以近似值的乘积，则进行匹配
and matching if we divide it by the products of the approximations the
products of the approximations the factorization q of x from j we're going
x从j的因式分解q，我们将得到该检查，您可以告诉
factorization q of x from j we're going to get that check okay and you can tell
to get that check okay and you can tell it's a normalization constant so we ask
这是一个归一化常数，所以我们问你
it's a normalization constant so we ask you
you the people's one so you get K so k is basically this normalization factor
在计算效用时将其归一化，因此使用归一化-如果您集成
距离数据，这样您就可以在屏幕上集成358的此产品
you the people's one so you get K so k is basically this normalization factor
你是人民的，所以你得到K所以k基本上就是这个归一化因子
is basically this normalization factor alright and we call this actually ZJ
好吧，我们称这实际上ZJ应该是
alright and we call this actually ZJ should be a big formulas for the
should be a big formulas for the expectation propagation algorithm is
期望传播算法就是您在底部看到的，所以
expectation propagation algorithm is what you see on the bottom alright so
what you see on the bottom alright so the idea is when the moment marching
想法是当行进的那一刻好吗，你们两个人被Q除
the idea is when the moment marching okay computer home you two divided by Q
okay computer home you two divided by Q minus a multiplied with the
减去乘以归一化因子的值必须是
minus a multiplied with the normalization factor must be a plate of
normalization factor must be a plate of us today what's it
我们今天是什么
好的，所以我将再次强调计算关键点的关键
normalization factor must be a plate of us today what's it
okay so I am going to emphasize again the key to key points right we compute
好的，所以我将再次强调计算关键点的关键
the key to key points right we compute its factor
它的因素还好，并不独立于其他因素
its factor all right not independent of the other
all right not independent of the other factors but in a way that the the
因素，但以某种方式让您的女演员占
factors but in a way that the the probability of your actresses accounted
probability of your actresses accounted in the approximation and we do this by
在近似中，我们通过不将此FJ学院的FJ与
in the approximation and we do this by not matching FJ this FJ Academy with the
not matching FJ this FJ Academy with the exact FJ but my matching Q theta with
确切的FJ，但我的匹配Q theta可以，所以我们没有做
exact FJ but my matching Q theta with this okay and so we don't have made the
this okay and so we don't have made the factor of J to start with will be the
开始的J因子将是theta的整个分布P
factor of J to start with will be the whole distribution P of theta and from
whole distribution P of theta and from that we can update the factor of J once
一旦完成，我们就可以更新J的因子，以及近似值
that we can update the factor of J once we're done and and the approximation
we're done and and the approximation again is given on the bottom so I had
再次在底部给出，所以我有服务，所以想一下就如你所知
again is given on the bottom so I had services so think of this as you know
services so think of this as you know let's say that this is the exact J
假设这是确切的J，这就是您所知道的
let's say that this is the exact J alright and this is what the you know
alright and this is what the you know doing so can you imagine a liberal and
这样做，您可以想象一个自由主义者，然后您尝试去掌握它，这有点像
doing so can you imagine a liberal and you try to master so this is sort of an
you try to master so this is sort of an right Victoria here if you try to
在维多利亚这里，如果您尝试进行优化以将其标记为蓝色
right Victoria here if you try to optimize a terribly to mark this blue
optimize a terribly to mark this blue distribution giving it something that
分布使它看起来像一个重磅炸弹，但
distribution giving it something that looks like a bombshell but the
looks like a bombshell but the distribution is this far away from her
分布离她的论文还很远，所以现在要做的是
distribution is this far away from her essay okay so now what that does is
essay okay so now what that does is impose the approximation of the factor
施加今天因素的近似值，以便在
impose the approximation of the factor today to be closer sampling between
today to be closer sampling between alright and the approximation for the
好吧，食物分配的近似值基本上就是
alright and the approximation for the food distribution basically terms it is
food distribution basically terms it is you know the probability you know the
你知道这个Q的非零概率域的概率
you know the probability you know the nonzero probability domain of this Q
nonzero probability domain of this Q minus a distribution so by the way you
减去分布，这样您就可以在这里看到我告诉的符号
minus a distribution so by the way you can see here the notation that I told
can see here the notation that I told you it is very common that abhorrest
你很常见，在描述什么是可恶的百万
you it is very common that abhorrest million you know in describing what is
million you know in describing what is going on so when you you know remember
因此，当您知道我们匹配时，我们会计算一个新的
going on so when you you know remember we we are matching we compute a new to
we we are matching we compute a new to narrow the manipulation of matching
用您所看到的分布来缩小匹配时刻的操纵范围
narrow the manipulation of matching moments with the distribution of you see
moments with the distribution of you see here inside the brackets is for the
这里的括号内是供投影操作员使用的
here inside the brackets is for the projection operator okay
projection operator okay so again you know you are extracting the
所以再次，您知道您正在提取时刻，然后尝试将其与
so again you know you are extracting the moments and you try to match this to the
moments and you try to match this to the corresponding Gaussian distribution okay
对应的高斯分布
corresponding Gaussian distribution okay okay
okay and so I will show you an example
因此，我将向您展示一个示例，其中此分布
and so I will show you an example actually where this distribution here
actually where this distribution here can be lets say Poisson distribution
可以这样说，当您对此进行近似时，泊松分布
can be lets say Poisson distribution when you have approximated with this
when you have approximated with this projection operator to a Gaussian
高斯投影算子
可能您还没想过的复杂性，何时
when you have approximated with this projection operator to a Gaussian
a complexity that maybe you haven't thought about this before okay and when
可能您还没想过的复杂性，何时
thought about this before okay and when here over this angle is this can be the
在这个角度上，这可以是祝福，但也可以是稳定的
here over this angle is this can be the blessing but also it can be stable a
blessing but also it can be stable a very painful process this exponential
非常痛苦的过程，这种指数形式给了他们所有权
very painful process this exponential form just gives them ownership all right
form just gives them ownership all right that's the most other example of
那是指数分布的另一个例子
that's the most other example of exponential distribution
exponential distribution occasionally thousand obviously this
偶尔，千种保护显然会给您提示，但是
occasionally thousand obviously this protection will give you the cue but is
protection will give you the cue but is also going to be Gaussian what happens
也将是高斯人，当他分裂成八卦时会发生什么
also going to be Gaussian what happens when he divide to gossip having
when he divide to gossip having discussed an equal in class before I
讨论过班级平等之前，我不会通过
discussed an equal in class before I will not have provided through no
will not have provided through no marginalization this conditional now we
边缘化这个条件现在我们有一个相对于高斯的关系
marginalization this conditional now we have a relative to Gaussian do you see
have a relative to Gaussian do you see any problem
任何问题
你高兴成千上万吗
have a relative to Gaussian do you see any problem
are you happy dividing into thousands
会发生什么
what can happen
例如或什么类型的新医疗发生了转变
such as or what type of new medical a shift
因为这个指数实际上我不认为被零除会
because this one exponents this actually I don't think the division by zero will
I don't think the division by zero will be a problem here okay because they're
这是个问题吧，因为它们是指数的
be a problem here okay because they're Exponential's
Exponential's but because you know functions you know
但是因为您知道功能，所以您知道
有兴趣执行这项权利，但在一天结束时，但这是一个
Exponential's but because you know functions you know
interested to enforce this right but at the end of the day but this is a
有兴趣执行这项权利，但在一天结束时，但这是一个
the end of the day but this is a Gaussian but some of the factors may
高斯，但其中一些因素实际上可能是负值
Gaussian but some of the factors may come to here actually a negative value
come to here actually a negative value okay and and you see this and you know
好的，您会看到这个，并且您知道您可能想实际使用这个
okay and and you see this and you know you may want to actually take this
you may want to actually take this former so didn't have time this morning
前者，所以今天早上没有时间再次验证他们十五。谢谢
former so didn't have time this morning to verify them again fifteen thank
to verify them again fifteen thank relationship the two gaussians okay you
关系两个高斯人好吧，你可以基本上得到一个气体和高斯
relationship the two gaussians okay you can you basically get a gas and Gaussian
can you basically get a gas and Gaussian right but you notice the variance is 1
是的，但是您注意到方差是V上的1减去V上的1等于
right but you notice the variance is 1 over V 1 minus 1 over V to the want of
over V 1 minus 1 over V to the want of the vision of the balances of numerator
分子和分母的平衡的愿景，显然这可以
the vision of the balances of numerator and denominator and obviously this can
and denominator and obviously this can be negative obviously can be negative
消极显然可以是消极好的，所以这又不是问题，而是如何
be negative obviously can be negative okay so again it is not an issue but how
okay so again it is not an issue but how you program this is something you need
您对此进行编程，需要非常谨慎，所以
you program this is something you need to be sort of very careful alright so
to be sort of very careful alright so these are not your everyday couch
这些不是你每天的沙发
因此，您是关于期望传播参与的新手示意图
to be sort of very careful alright so these are not your everyday couch
so you a novice schematic on this participation of expectation propagation
因此，您是关于期望传播参与的新手示意图
participation of expectation propagation on the tester problem that I introduced
关于我介绍的测试仪问题，我将讨论这个问题
on the tester problem that I introduced and I'm going to discuss this problem
and I'm going to discuss this problem expensively and the topics is basically
价格昂贵，主题基本上就是您得到的苏联近似值
expensively and the topics is basically the Soviet approximation that you get
the Soviet approximation that you get when the context for the support of X 2
当X 2减去J分布的支持上下文减少了
when the context for the support of X 2 minus J distribution that reduces the
minus J distribution that reduces the bar down distribution could you do the
向下分布吧，您可以在前两张图片中进行计算吗？
bar down distribution could you do the computation in the top two pictures is
computation in the top two pictures is narrow all right so you can see the this
缩小范围，这样您就可以看到此分布是上下文
narrow all right so you can see the this this distribution here is the context
this distribution here is the context this is the Q minus J okay
这是Q减去J，可以，您可以根据此处显示的是
this is the Q minus J okay and you can depending here to show is
and you can depending here to show is that the actual approximation of the
我们最终使用的J因子的实际近似值
that the actual approximation of the factor of J that we do eventually with
factor of J that we do eventually with expectation propagation it is only good
期望传播只有在Q支持的区域才是好的
expectation propagation it is only good in the region where the support of Q
in the region where the support of Q minus J is nonzero okay so you can see
减J为非零好，所以您可以在其他任何地方看到
minus J is nonzero okay so you can see everywhere else
everywhere else right the approximation is very large
对了，这个近似值非常大，这是非常非常的，你知道吗，所以
right the approximation is very large this is a very this is you know okay so
this is a very this is you know okay so here the approximation is good and the
这里的近似值很好，你知道这里的支持是
here the approximation is good and the same you know the support here is
same you know the support here is nonzero there you can see how good the
非零，您可以看到蓝色的逼近度有多好，什么是
nonzero there you can see how good the approximation looks the blue and what is
approximation looks the blue and what is it the the red they basically coincide
红色，它们基本上在这里重合，现在您有一个杯子了
it the the red they basically coincide here now you have a mug out the context
here now you have a mug out the context that is much wider so you notice the
那要宽得多，所以您注意到它不再是的近似值是
that is much wider so you notice the approximation that it's not anymore is
approximation that it's not anymore is good right because this is very wide
好的权利，因为这是很广泛的，这是可以预期的
good right because this is very wide this is to be expected
this is to be expected all right and similarly here yeah the
好吧，在这里类似，是的，近似值开始基本偏离
all right and similarly here yeah the approximation starts deviating basically
approximation starts deviating basically it's not very good over the support so
在支持方面不是很好，所以如果您的支持范围很窄
it's not very good over the support so if you have a narrow support right
if you have a narrow support right assuming you do inference right if your
如果您的问题遍及整个领域，并且假设您推理正确，
assuming you do inference right if your problems all over the space and you have
problems all over the space and you have no data the issue that you get in
没有数据，您在事后估算中遇到的问题
no data the issue that you get in posterior estimation
posterior estimation all right for the last time all the
最后一次没事吧
all right for the last time all the other
other we're going to be moving away from this
我们将摆脱这种困扰，所以这就是它的样子
we're going to be moving away from this okay so this is what it looks
okay so this is what it looks if you initialize all the factors right
如果您初始化了所有因素，那么通常必须先从某些方面入手
if you initialize all the factors right you have to start with something usually
you have to start with something usually if you can just put them all the big
如果你能把所有的大外星人都带进去，那么暴力就是这样
if you can just put them all the big aliens with some in and violence's so
aliens with some in and violence's so this is your approximation for the whole
这是整个后验分布的近似值，然后开始
this is your approximation for the whole posterior distribution then you start
posterior distribution then you start updating one faster at the time you
在您记得的时候更新一个快到十二个腔
updating one faster at the time you remember to twelve this cavity
remember to twelve this cavity distribution Q minus J okay by dividing
分配Q减去J可以，将Q自由度除以您做的Jake因子
distribution Q minus J okay by dividing Q freedom with a factor of Jake you do
Q freedom with a factor of Jake you do one with matching two completely new you
一个与两个完全匹配的匹配，您可以为该计算归一化部分
one with matching two completely new you compute this normalization part for the
compute this normalization part for the update part of them is given by what you
更新部分是由您所看到的给出，而不是您选择了所有
update part of them is given by what you see instead be you picked all the
see instead be you picked all the factors okay obviously you know if
好的因素很明显，您知道您是否要继续迭代多个
factors okay obviously you know if you're gonna keep iterating multiple
you're gonna keep iterating multiple runs to be sure that let's efficient
运行以确保让我们有效地推进主要的方差
runs to be sure that let's efficient advances that the main of the variances
advances that the main of the variances of this approximation is don't change
这个近似值不会随着迭代而改变，一旦完成，您就可以
of this approximation is don't change with iteration and once you're done you
with iteration and once you're done you can actually calculate the mobile
实际上也可以计算移动证据的自由权，所以这
can actually calculate the mobile evidence as well for free right so this
evidence as well for free right so this would be something useful for model
对于模型选择等您可能会有用的东西
would be something useful for model selection and the likes that you may be
selection and the likes that you may be interested to do the magnets is there is
有兴趣做磁铁的人，没有证据表明它会正常工作，并且
interested to do the magnets is there is no proof of this will ever work okay and
它会追逐正确，但事实证明还不错
it will chasten right but it's not proof okay
在期望传播中有很多理论，但是你知道
there's a lot of theory that goes under the expectation propagation but you know
the expectation propagation but you know you know so if you tomorrow come with a
你知道吗，如果你明天要来一份新的PA统计资料，并证明
you know so if you tomorrow come with a new PA statistics and you demonstrate
new PA statistics and you demonstrate something about the convergence of the
关于金属会聚的事，每个人都会读你的
something about the convergence of the metals everybody will be reading your
metals everybody will be reading your paper because this is sort of still a
论文，因为这仍然是当今世界中非常重要的研究课题
paper because this is sort of still a very important research topic in the
very important research topic in the literature all right so I think that
没事的文学，所以我认为那将显示您的期望
literature all right so I think that that would show you the expectation
that would show you the expectation propagation result so if I remember
传播结果，因此，如果我再次记得，我们将近似这个更暗的
propagation result so if I remember again we are approximating this darker
again we are approximating this darker region this is the Laplace appreciation
这是拉普拉斯地区的鉴赏
最小化，我们得到了基于变分的
again we are approximating this darker region this is the Laplace appreciation
minimization we got variational based
植物还可以，所以在EP中，这就是我所知道的值的变化
the plants okay so in the EP so this is the variation of values which I know
the variation of values which I know what color is all right and the blue is
什么颜色都可以，蓝色是我们所期望的
what color is all right and the blue is the one that we get with expectation
the one that we get with expectation propagation the trusox are different
trusox的传播今晚有所不同，但在这种情况下，如果我
propagation the trusox are different tonight but in this particular case if I
tonight but in this particular case if I see correctly right the support of the
正确看对EP解决方案的支持远不止一种
see correctly right the support of the EP solution is much broader than the one
EP solution is much broader than the one you get with variational values okay so
您可以得到变化值，所以取决于，当然这是一个交流电
you get with variational values okay so depending on and of course this is an AC
depending on and of course this is an AC distribution if you try to do this for
分布，如果您尝试对复杂的省份这样做，答案可能是
distribution if you try to do this for complicated province the answers may be
complicated province the answers may be completely different
完全不同
好吧，我要给你这个时钟，这张幻灯片上给出了证明，所以
complicated province the answers may be completely different
okay I'm gonna give you this as a clock the proof is given on this slide so
好吧，我要给你这个时钟，这张幻灯片上给出了证明，所以
the proof is given on this slide so suppose you know you so you have a
假设您认识您，因此您可以对后部进行自定义，因此您
suppose you know you so you have a customization of your posterior so you
customization of your posterior so you have the four times each of the
收集数据时，每个似然性温度要进行四次
have the four times each of the likelihood temps as you collect data
likelihood temps as you collect data right so for the prior that you started
对，因此对于您之前开始的操作，让它通过，它会告诉您是否
right so for the prior that you started with so let this pass it shows you if
with so let this pass it shows you if you start an approximation the exact
你开始一个近似值，确切的值不会改变，只是一个姐姐
you start an approximation the exact value will not change that just a sister
value will not change that just a sister and it gives you something else
它给你带来了其他不确定的东西，所以如果你在这里
and it gives you something else not sure will be public so here if you
not sure will be public so here if you know let's say the prior you can set
知道，假设您可以将其设置为等于先验，而您不会
know let's say the prior you can set this equal to the prior and you don't
this equal to the prior and you don't have to worry you can fit all the
不必担心您可以将所有因素拟合得一样，因为该算法
have to worry you can fit all the factors the same because the algorithm
factors the same because the algorithm will not update effectively this factor
不会有效地更新这个零因子，你知道我的意思是它将有
will not update effectively this factor of zero you know I mean it will have
of zero you know I mean it will have needed but it would still give you the
需要，但仍会给您相同的答案
needed but it would still give you the same answer
现在大概有20年前有一种与黄金有关的金属，但实际上并非如此
now there is the metal about gold maybe 20 years ago but they are not actually
20 years ago but they are not actually in any expectation propagation
在任何期望传播算法中，
in any expectation propagation algorithms but the sort of try to take
algorithms but the sort of try to take advantage of this factorization to do
这种分解的优点是可以做一些类似的近似
advantage of this factorization to do some similar type of approximations and
some similar type of approximations and the metal overhead with amounts of
具有参考量的金属开销就是这个假设的密度
the metal overhead with amounts of references is this assumed density
references is this assumed density filtering method of unity in machine
机器学习书籍中统一性的过滤方法，但并不完全相同
filtering method of unity in machine learning books but they're not exactly
learning books but they're not exactly EP story P is basically the nearest
EP故事P基本上是最接近的近似值，可以访问的网站
EP story P is basically the nearest approximation and okay the website which
approximation and okay the website which is the guy that actually the expectation
其实期望传播令人难以置信的人是麻省理工学院许多
is the guy that actually the expectation propagation is disbelief is but MIT many
propagation is disbelief is but MIT many years ago this thesis was like 30 pages
几年前，这篇论文大概有30页，我们一直在研究
years ago this thesis was like 30 pages we have been about play revisions of
we have been about play revisions of this business after graduation you know
毕业后的这项业务，您知道您必须要修改的胡萝卜
this business after graduation you know what you must have carrots to revise
what you must have carrots to revise your taste after you graduate right you
毕业后的品味好吧，通常你躲在桌子底下，不是他
your taste after you graduate right you usually you hide under the table no he's
usually you hide under the table no he's not hiding because he knows people are
不躲藏，因为他知道人们正在读它，他会去修改正确的公式
not hiding because he knows people are reading it he goes and correct formulas
reading it he goes and correct formulas improved here there it's always existed
改善这里一直存在
improved here there it's always existed okay
okay you can obviously refer to either
如果您在网络上发送邮件，您显然可以引用其中一个
you can obviously refer to either actually if you sent on the web you will
actually if you sent on the web you will find very high numbers of citations for
找到了很多被引用的作品，但我唯一想做的就是
find very high numbers of citations for this work but the only thing I wanted to
this work but the only thing I wanted to tell you is very much of promise lots of
告诉您，非常有前途的AP金属来源会带来很多玩具问题
tell you is very much of promise lots of toy problems the AP metal source
toy problems the AP metal source comparison straight basically that there
直接比较，基本上有愚蠢的或另外二十个
comparison straight basically that there are stupid or twenty of the other
are stupid or twenty of the other methods we have seen up to now including
到目前为止，我们所见过的方法包括许多指标，其中包括
methods we have seen up to now including that many metrics including that include
that many metrics including that include particle or MCMC type approximation
粒子或MCMC类型的近似值，因此您可以在此处看到
particle or MCMC type approximation so you can see here the petal in the
so you can see here the petal in the approximation would be P is the best
近似地，P基本上是最好的，因为您知道a的变化是
approximation would be P is the best basically for you know variation of a is
basically for you know variation of a is something most important something in
在照明系统分析论文领域中最重要的事情
something most important something in the light system analysis papers domain
the light system analysis papers domain kosoul's that you can actually pose this
kosoul是您实际上可以提出期望和最大化的问题
kosoul's that you can actually pose this problem of expectation and maximization
problem of expectation and maximization as the problem of minimizing energy
作为使能量函数最小化的问题，所以这非常好
as the problem of minimizing energy function right and so it's very nice
function right and so it's very nice alright so the result of an optimization
好了，所以状态的优化版本的结果您知道这是什么
alright so the result of an optimization version of state you know this is what
version of state you know this is what the problem is is minimization of some
问题是最小化某些功能，不幸的是，没有这样的功能
the problem is is minimization of some function unfortunately there is no such
function unfortunately there is no such a thing as working with the lower bound
与我们看到您的下限一起工作的事情可能会实现，但
a thing as working with the lower bound that we saw you may be realized but the
that we saw you may be realized but the measurement we need the latest increase
测量，我们需要最新的增加，所以在这里，如果你这样做的话，这就是他的精力
measurement we need the latest increase so here if you do here's his energy
so here if you do here's his energy function where you do if iterations this
函数在哪里执行迭代，这绝对没有证据，没有理由
function where you do if iterations this absolutely no proof no reason why that
absolutely no proof no reason why that energy function will actually be
能量函数实际上将被最大化，并且将是单调的
energy function will actually be maximized and it will be monotonically
会收敛，然后达到该能量常数的平稳值，因此，如果得到一个
converges then you reach the stationary of this energy constant so if you get a
of this energy constant so if you get a solution that's the right solution what
是正确的解决方案，市长福克斯之间会发生什么
solution that's the right solution what happens in between its mayor Fox okay
非常大，向您展示可能适用于令人生畏的问题的API
so very big to show you possibly API which works for face daunting problem
which works for face daunting problem and then we will love definitely we have
然后，我们一定会爱上几分钟，所以我可以告诉您
and then we will love definitely we have a few minutes so I can tell you on
a few minutes so I can tell you on extending this to to publish the
扩展到发布图形模型，这样我们就可以
extending this to to publish the graphical models so we can make
graphical models so we can make connections with other algorithms so I
与其他算法的连接，所以我知道问题在于我们只想
connections with other algorithms so I know that the problem is we only want to
know that the problem is we only want to compute the the mean of this Gaussian so
计算这个高斯的平均值，所以我们收集数据，但是数据基本上
compute the the mean of this Gaussian so we collect data but the data basically
we collect data but the data basically are noisy because some of the data may
之所以嘈杂，是因为某些数据可能来自这三位元
are noisy because some of the data may be coming from this three bit dollars in
be coming from this three bit dollars in the submission but some of them can be
提交，但其中一些可能来自擅自占地者分布，所以
the submission but some of them can be coming from the squatter distribution so
coming from the squatter distribution so it can be completely relevant to the
它可能与您想要估计的平均值完全相关，所以
it can be completely relevant to the mean that you want to estimate okay so
mean that you want to estimate okay so that's why this is called the clattering
这就是为什么我们将其称为“拍手问题”的原因
that's why this is called the clattering problem we're going to put some prior on
problem we're going to put some prior on the parameters theta
参数theta显然是UH归一化后验
the parameters theta obviously the UH normalized posterior
obviously the UH normalized posterior looks like this it's like if we turbine
看起来像这样，如果我们的涡轮是高斯混合气，那么您有2个
looks like this it's like if we turbine is a Gaussian mixture so you have 2 to
is a Gaussian mixture so you have 2 to the N terms so this is not something if
N个词，所以这不是什么可以与您一起使用的，因此您可以在此处查看是否
the N terms so this is not something if you can work with so you can see here if
you can work with so you can see here if this is the to really Gaussian that you
这是您要提取平均值的真正的高斯模型
this is the to really Gaussian that you want to extract the mean a lots of data
want to extract the mean a lots of data concentrate here but you have a lots of
集中在这里，但您有很多数据，但与此无关
concentrate here but you have a lots of data but have nothing to do with this
data but have nothing to do with this particular means so you want to be able
特殊的方式，所以您希望能够进行推断，所以我建议
particular means so you want to be able to do inference so I that I recommend
to do inference so I that I recommend that you make this problem because you
您会遇到这个问题，因为您知道我们提到了
that you make this problem because you know we mentioned things becoming
know we mentioned things becoming Gaussian like distributions with
如果您可以知道是否具有负方差的高斯分布
Gaussian like distributions with negative variance if you can you know if
negative variance if you can you know if you look at the bra on this problem and
您看一下这个问题的胸罩，然后尝试实施它，那么我们就有一个
you look at the bra on this problem and you try to implement it then we have a
you try to implement it then we have a Python code you will see why there are
Python代码，您将看到为什么那里存在问题，所以我希望您实际
Python code you will see why there are problems there so I want you to actually
problems there so I want you to actually move algebra at the algebra is not very
在代数上移动代数不是很困难，证明在幻灯片中
move algebra at the algebra is not very difficult the proofs are in the slides
difficult the proofs are in the slides so what we are going to do is I'm just
所以我们要做的就是总结我们要取得的结果
so what we are going to do is I'm just gonna summarize the results we are going
gonna summarize the results we are going to take an approximation of pure theta
将纯θ近似为多元高斯模型
to take an approximation of pure theta to be a multivariate Gaussian okay
to be a multivariate Gaussian okay obviously this means the factors will be
显然，这意味着因素也会
obviously this means the factors will be also
also thousands but in the spirit of what we
数以千计，但本着我们讨论过的关于道奇的负面思想
thousands but in the spirit of what we discussed about Dodgers with negative
discussed about Dodgers with negative audience we are aggressive response of
观众，我们正在积极地进行耐力冥想护理，并且
audience we are aggressive response of stamina meditation care and and the
stamina meditation care and and the square exponential here for effectively
此处平方平方有效地表示方差二元可以为负，因此
square exponential here for effectively that variance bien can be negative so
that variance bien can be negative so this notion I have been looking at them
我一直在研究发行版的这个想法将是颠倒的
this notion I have been looking at them on distribution would be upside down
on distribution would be upside down okay so you need to start this away from
好的，所以您需要从一些初始化开始，例如
okay so you need to start this away from with some initialization and for example
with some initialization and for example you can say of this factors to be equal
你可以说这个因素等于一个
you can say of this factors to be equal to one
to one that's what is discussed here okay this
这就是这里讨论的内容，好吧，假设金属做的也一样
that's what is discussed here okay this assume immensely metal does the same
assume immensely metal does the same thing in approximating the fastest when
停下来时最快的事情就是什么，所以你需要一些东西
thing in approximating the fastest when you stop so you need to have something
you stop so you need to have something to start with okay you follow the Eiger
首先，如果您要更新，请遵循Eiger会说一个
to start with okay you follow the Eiger if you're going to update would say one
if you're going to update would say one factor you form this cavity this
因素，你形成这个腔这种情况，你的计算机组织你
factor you form this cavity this condition you computer organization you
condition you computer organization you do moment marching you point in you and
马上进去，指向你，然后你就有一个因素，所以
do moment marching you point in you and then you have there is a factor so the
then you have there is a factor so the question is if you have beta factor what
问题是，如果您有β因子，则a的均值和方差是多少
question is if you have beta factor what will be the mean and the variance of a
will be the mean and the variance of a factor and the ancestors are the five
因素和祖先是五克拉的戒指，也许可以给这个
factor and the ancestors are the five carat ring slide maybe giving this
给我一秒钟的空间，就可以知道我以为有两个梦想
give me one second okay sterically the you know I thought there's two dreams
you know I thought there's two dreams like having all the answers so if you
像拥有所有答案一样，所以如果您先计算空腔
like having all the answers so if you compute first the cavity the
compute first the cavity the distribution it comes to be a Gaussian
分布就变成了高斯像这样，是逆方差是
distribution it comes to be a Gaussian like this is the inverse variance is the
like this is the inverse variance is the precision how it looks like okay this is
精度看起来如何，这是主要的问题。归一化因子
precision how it looks like okay this is the main okay the normalization factor
the main okay the normalization factor you can compute as well and and then you
您也可以进行计算，然后必须进行更新，这样您就可以
you can compute as well and and then you have to update you okay and you can so
have to update you okay and you can so actually the updates of can you they
实际上，您能看到他们的更新吗？实际上，您知道吗？
actually the updates of can you they look and actually they updates you know
look and actually they updates you know I'm looking on top will end here so the
我想在这里结束就好了，所以六月的更新看起来
I'm looking on top will end here so the updates of June you look the way that
updates of June you look the way that you see them here very nice clean
你在这里看到他们很好的干净公式，实际上这个系数
you see them here very nice clean formula where actually this coefficient
formula where actually this coefficient looks like the probability of the point
看起来像点X的概率而不是绘图仪还可以
looks like the probability of the point X and not being a plotter okay
X and not being a plotter okay so again an analytical expression for
因此再次对社区的这些含义进行了分析
so again an analytical expression for this these mean of the community
this these mean of the community distribution is knowing the variance of
分布知道kayuu分布的方差也就是
distribution is knowing the variance of the kayuu distribution is also known a
the kayuu distribution is also known a little early to page slides of the
关系或计算开始于页面幻灯片的提早开始
little early to page slides of the relation or the calculation start in
relation or the calculation start in right and and if you you have the
对，如果您有分布，您就会知道像您一样的高斯人
right and and if you you have the distribution you know gaussians like you
distribution you know gaussians like you can update it after and the updates of
以后可以更新它，其中一部分的更新是有潜力的
can update it after and the updates of the part of them are spirits potentials
the part of them are spirits potentials like that as before the mean is given by
像以前一样，这个漂亮的表达式给出了均值
like that as before the mean is given by this nice expression the precision
this nice expression the precision variance is given like this so the
这样就产生了差异，因此警察跳过了总的问题或
variance is given like this so the police jumped on the total problem or
police jumped on the total problem or analytical so actually you can see sort
分析性的，所以实际上您可以看到这种方程式，您知道
analytical so actually you can see sort of this equation you know
of this equation you know in with written Amish there are no perks
在书面的阿米什语中，没有特殊的待遇，非医学近似也可以
in with written Amish there are no perks maesters non-medical approximation okay
maesters non-medical approximation okay you can actually calculate the model
您最终还可以通过分析来实际计算模型证据
you can actually calculate the model evidence as well analytically at the end
evidence as well analytically at the end of the day one of the whole thing
一天的整体融合和弹性的项目代码
of the day one of the whole thing converges and the resilient item code
converges and the resilient item code that you can allow for this type of
您可以考虑这种类型的问题
that you can allow for this type of problem
problem and mr. t Rizal Park sorry that what you
和先生t黎刹公园（Rizal Park）对不起，您在这里寻求的东西可以为您运动
and mr. t Rizal Park sorry that what you seek here this can you motion for you
seek here this can you motion for you upside down all right why not I mean you
颠倒了好吧，为什么我不是说你得到指甲花的家伙，所有这就是为什么
upside down all right why not I mean you get the henna guys and all there was why
get the henna guys and all there was why not okay
不行
再次，这是FN，这是近似因子违规，所以你是
get the henna guys and all there was why not okay
again this is FN this is the approximation factor offense so you're
再次，这是FN，这是近似因子违规，所以你是
approximation factor offense so you're not this year it's not really that you
不是今年，不是真的要用笔监控
not this year it's not really that you are trying to monitor this with a pen
are trying to monitor this with a pen you are trying to actually concentrate
您正在尝试真正地集中在该支持所在的地区
you are trying to actually concentrate in the region where the support of this
in the region where the support of this cavity distribution is which is here and
空腔分布在这里，这就是近似值
cavity distribution is which is here and that's what the approximation it's good
that's what the approximation it's good the rest there's nothing you can do
剩下的就没事做，从某种意义上说你不做
the rest there's nothing you can do about okay and in some sense you don't
about okay and in some sense you don't really care and similarly in this case
真的很在乎，在这种情况下，罪犯在这里，你可以看到
really care and similarly in this case the convict is here that you can see the
the convict is here that you can see the two approximation is not very well
两个近似不是很好，几乎在那个区域它们重合，所以
two approximation is not very well almost they coincide in that region so
almost they coincide in that region so it's actually for the clutter problem
实际上是为了解决混乱的问题，它们是Python代码的一部分，因此
it's actually for the clutter problem they are in part of the Python code so
they are in part of the Python code so you can if you do variation of a is you
如果可以做a的变体，则可以使用拉普拉斯逼近法
you can if you do variation of a is you use Laplace approximation you can push
use Laplace approximation you can push it to as many days as you want to
它要花很多天，基本上可以有效传播
it to as many days as you want to basically it's proficient propagation
basically it's proficient propagation through this problem performance the
通过这个问题表现最好
through this problem performance the best okay
best okay institutional coming around this
机构解决了这个棘手的问题，因为他非常
institutional coming around this grappling problem because he was very
grappling problem because he was very easily programming they need to be
轻松编程，他们需要完成所有分析工作，
easily programming they need to be completing everything was analytical and
completing everything was analytical and it was also a problem quite if he comes
如果他能做到最好的话，这也是一个问题，也许你可以
it was also a problem quite if he comes to some of the best okay maybe you can
to some of the best okay maybe you can do a problem that it becomes this for
做一个问题，这对你来说不是最好的
do a problem that it becomes this for you are not the best
好的，因为我们基本上是在更新与
okay we have because we basically be updating information related to
updating information related to variables X 1 and X 2 ok nothing else
变量X 1和X 2没关系，因此可以以某种方式设想没有
variables X 1 and X 2 ok nothing else so can somehow envision that there is no
so can somehow envision that there is no expectation propagation language that's
期望传播语言，这就是今天演讲的标题的原因
expectation propagation language that's why the title of the presentation today
why the title of the presentation today was local variation fluctuations where
是局部变化的波动，整个事物以某种方式崩溃
was local variation fluctuations where somehow the whole thing collapses to
somehow the whole thing collapses to allow us to do an update here and update
允许我们在这里进行更新并在那里更新并更新他们的等等，甚至
allow us to do an update here and update there and update their etc and even
there and update their etc and even further actually if you so let's say
实际上，如果您这样说x1 x2的理论函数，也许您
further actually if you so let's say a theorist function of x1 x2 maybe you
a theorist function of x1 x2 maybe you can even fertilize this 2 factor of x 1
甚至可以施肥2倍x 1，所以你可以有一个聚酯
can even fertilize this 2 factor of x 1 so you can have a polyester
so you can have a polyester approximation as 1/4 - 20 X 1 and in all
近似为1/4-20 X 1以及所有X 2的因数，类似地，在这里
approximation as 1/4 - 20 X 1 and in all factor of X 2 and similarly here did you
factor of X 2 and similarly here did you have something else on a function of X 2
X 2的功能还有其他功能X 4的功能可以更新吗
have something else on a function of X 2 the function of X 4 can you update each
the function of X 4 can you update each of them separately
他们每个人都可以，您可以更新每个人吗
of them separately ok can you update each of them
ok can you update each of them separately - it's amazing you will say
分开-令人惊讶的是，您会说我能猜出答案是，您是
separately - it's amazing you will say that I can figure the answer is yes you
that I can figure the answer is yes you can and then we will see everything we
可以，然后我们将看到我们学到的有关影响图形的所有信息
can and then we will see everything we learn about influencing graphs in
learn about influencing graphs in particularly ideas of you know master
尤其是您知道主间隔和传播所有这些的想法
particularly ideas of you know master spacing and propagation all of these
spacing and propagation all of these cases are
情况是
好吧，只是为了简单起见，您可以分解因子或动物群，但是
spacing and propagation all of these cases are
ok ok just to make things simple you can be factorized or groups of animals but
好吧，只是为了简单起见，您可以分解因子或动物群，但是
be factorized or groups of animals but right now let's take you to the top four
现在，让我们带您到前四眼，并使用Z型猴子攻击
right now let's take you to the top four eyes and using a monkey - of Z to attack
eyes and using a monkey - of Z to attack alright so we want to minimize this
好吧，所以我们想最小化P和Q距离的遍历K，所以我是
alright so we want to minimize this Traverse K of distance of P and Q so I'm
Traverse K of distance of P and Q so I'm writing this the definition - P of
写这个定义-更长的P的P
writing this the definition - P of longer pupae
longer pupae right or like be longer Peele
对还是喜欢更长的Peele /在那里治愈我们好吧Scott
right or like be longer Peele / cured us about there okay Scott
/ cured us about there okay Scott so we need less time doing ads about now
因此，我们需要更少的时间来做广告，以了解现在的生活使命是
so we need less time doing ads about now the mission of a life is living as a
the mission of a life is living as a poet with two eyes that are conscious of
诗人，有两只眼睛，对紫子有意识，所以因为我在这里有一个和尚，你
poet with two eyes that are conscious of Zi so because I have a monk here you
Zi so because I have a monk here you agree with me that there Nathan would
我同意弥敦道会给我减去B的Z的总和。
agree with me that there Nathan would give me minus B of Z summation of the
give me minus B of Z summation of the level choice of Zi all right yes
Zi的水平选择可以-宝贝爱鸦片给我熵
level choice of Zi all right yes - babe love opium gives me the entropy I
- babe love opium gives me the entropy I don't care there is no dependence on you
不在乎没有对您的依赖，所以我将只确定
don't care there is no dependence on you so I am going to identify only the
so I am going to identify only the proper QJ because this is what I am
适当的QJ，因为这是您要更新时要更新的内容
proper QJ because this is what I am going to update while you are going to
going to update while you are going to see what is the effective to j1 we
看看什么对j1有效，我们最小化了这个监听，所以我只想
see what is the effective to j1 we minimize this listen so I am only take
minimize this listen so I am only take 2j the rest of the terms don't depend on
2j其余术语不取决于我不在乎的情况，或者我是特朗普
2j the rest of the terms don't depend on the situation I don't care or I Trump
the situation I don't care or I Trump I'm going to rewrite this nice thing as
我将把这个好东西重写为-fitzy好吧，我打算
I'm going to rewrite this nice thing as - fitzy all right and I'm going to
- fitzy all right and I'm going to integrate all the Bible since the except
整合除J之外的所有圣经，所以你能告诉我这个分布吗
integrate all the Bible since the except J so can you tell me this distribution
J so can you tell me this distribution this integral what this tribution is it
这个积分是什么贡献，所以当你取Z的P时，
this integral what this tribution is it so when you take P of Z and you
so when you take P of Z and you integrate everything out but sorry
整合所有内容，但是对不起，当您取P为0时会得到什么
integrate everything out but sorry what do you get so when you take P of 0
what do you get so when you take P of 0 integrate all the variables for J
整合J的所有变量
蒙苏诺（Monsuno）上山，您认识ZJ先生。丰特诺
what do you get so when you take P of 0 integrate all the variables for J
the Monsuno you get the mountain on you know ZJ mr. Fontenot
蒙苏诺（Monsuno）上山，您认识ZJ先生。丰特诺
know ZJ mr. Fontenot alright so ridiculous dimanche though
好吧，可笑的鬼话虽然好吧，所以这真的是时刻
alright so ridiculous dimanche though alright so this is really the moments
alright so this is really the moments ago fine okay and so now we need to
以前很好，所以现在我们需要最小化它，这是
ago fine okay and so now we need to minimize this it's a functional of the
minimize this it's a functional of the optimization problem you cannot just
优化问题你不能仅仅把河水分别用一个
optimization problem you cannot just take the river to respective use a so
take the river to respective use a so you need to and of course but QJ is
您当然需要，但是QJ已标准化
you need to and of course but QJ is normalized
好吧好吧，对像你这样的因素有一个近似值
okay okay makes sense to have approximation for its factors like you
approximation for its factors like you know if a caveat because it's a trap
知道是否有警告，因为它是一个陷阱，实际上是在个人中
know if a caveat because it's a trap secretly and in actually the individual
secretly and in actually the individual component inside is part of so a very
内部组件是X的232 FB 252 f p3之一的一部分
component inside is part of so a very one of its one of a 232 FB 252 f p3 of X
one of its one of a 232 FB 252 f p3 of X 3 etcetera okay so that way we have a
3 etcetera好的，这样我们有二十个因式分解
3 etcetera okay so that way we have a twenty factorized
好吧，所以我们想最小化出生分布和X的Q之间的距离
okay so we want to minimize the distance between birth distribution and Q of X
然后从那里我们将为此部分提出一个更新
and then from there we're going to come up with an update for this part by
up with an update for this part by dividing by the cavity distribution an
除以型腔分布，我们需要带来一个优化问题
dividing by the cavity distribution an optimization problem is we need to bring
optimization problem is we need to bring this distribution as close as possible
此分配尽可能接近此分配权限
this distribution as close as possible to this distribution right
to this distribution right okay can you pay me based on what we saw
好吧，您能根据我们在这里看到的情况向我付款吗，让我们听听我的优化信息
okay can you pay me based on what we saw here let's listen to my optimization
here let's listen to my optimization problem
因此，如果您错过了分配问题中的最小化错过
so if you missed the minimize missed from the mention of distribution
操作出来，他们必须能够工作，所以他们必须
operations that come out that they have to be able to work so this they have to
to be able to work so this they have to be equal to given as you know the
等于给定，因为您知道模块化提交原始内容的动机
be equal to given as you know the motivation the modular submit original
motivation the modular submit original this the Mazda mx-5 is just this stuff
这个马自达mx-5就是这个东西，边际效应是什么
this the Mazda mx-5 is just this stuff alright what's the marginal effects
alright what's the marginal effects customers extra fee RS the X 2 this is X
客户额外费用RS X 2这是X 3，所以如果这是与某人X 3
customers extra fee RS the X 2 this is X 3 so if is this for with someone X 3
3 so if is this for with someone X 3 what is the mountain X 3 I see on in
我在这个学期中看到的山峰X 3是什么，所以我们必须整合
what is the mountain X 3 I see on in this term here so we have to integrate
this term here so we have to integrate no extreme twist anything else
没有极端的扭曲
对不起，我没注意
this term here so we have to integrate no extreme twist anything else
I'm sorry I wasn't paying attention
[音乐]
[Music]
好吧，任何会消失的东西，请确保我们得到了，我们得到了
okay anything that will disappear so make sure that we get this we get the
make sure that we get this we get the update that is the summation X 3 of f DX
更新是f DX 2 3的总和X 3，这就是全部
update that is the summation X 3 of f DX 2 3 all right which is this down all
2 3 all right which is this down all right and then this their FB 3 ok FP 3
对，然后他们的FB 3 ok FP 3减小了这里的总和
right and then this their FB 3 ok FP 3 is a decreased this summation here
我们得到了更新的日期和FB 3的日期
we get the update of being this and the date of FB 3
date of FB 3 being done now let's concentrate because
现在，让我们集中精力，因为我们只有两分钟的时间
being done now let's concentrate because we only have two minutes on this
we only have two minutes on this equation tells me if it reminds you
等式告诉我是否可以提醒您任何事情，如果P可以执行此操作
equation tells me if it reminds you anything at all so by doing this if P
anything at all so by doing this if P and effectively moment maps interesting
并有效地使时刻图有趣
[音乐]
anything at all so by doing this if P and effectively moment maps interesting
[Music]
[音乐]
这是没有道理的，要知道X 2在此点向下，这部分的意义是
[Music]
this is no sense to know X 2 dot this down here and this part the sense to
这是没有道理的，要知道X 2在此点向下，这部分的意义是
down here and this part the sense to know X 2 which is various and then I
知道X 2是各种各样的，然后我考虑这个因子，它是
know X 2 which is various and then I take this factor which is a function of
take this factor which is a function of X 2 and X 3 and it's a great house X 2
X 2和X 3，这是一个很棒的房子X 2你知道我得到了我得到的消息
X 2 and X 3 and it's a great house X 2 you know what I get I get the message
you know what I get I get the message that is propagated to excrete okay so
传播到粪便就可以了，所以基本上信念传播是
that is propagated to excrete okay so basically belief propagation comes as a
basically belief propagation comes as a trivial exercise of expectation
琐碎的期望练习会传播，好吧，您知道的不只是真的
trivial exercise of expectation propagates okay you know not just really
propagates okay you know not just really expect it right but it's just one of
期望它是对的，但这只是这些奇迹之一
expect it right but it's just one of these miracles of
these miracles of of mathematics and ingenuity and stimuli
您可以购物或查看所有恐怖的数学，巧思和刺激知识
of mathematics and ingenuity and stimuli you can shop or view all the terror okay
you can shop or view all the terror okay I suggest that you look at the slides I
我建议您看一下幻灯片，我没有时间进一步讨论
I suggest that you look at the slides I don't have time to discuss this further
don't have time to discuss this further you can extend this this two very
您可以扩展这两个非常重要的位置，也许这​​个关键需要
you can extend this this two very important maybe this key needs to be
important maybe this key needs to be discussed on Thursday but basically if
在星期四讨论过，但基本上，如果可以将其扩展到一般的信念
discussed on Thursday but basically if you can extend this to general belief
you can extend this to general belief propagation okay and you can share that
传播还可以，你可以分享
知识和这种功能障碍，因此每个音符的底边分开
you can extend this to general belief propagation okay and you can share that
knowledge and this dysfunction so where the bottom edge of each note separatory
知识和这种功能障碍，因此每个音符的底边分开
the bottom edge of each note separatory all right you can update this variable
好的，您可以更新此可变量，例如，波长
all right you can update this variable amount for example and the wave length
amount for example and the wave length is variable along when we did you know
当我们知道传递时，变量是可变的，因此我们接受了所有的消息，
is variable along when we did you know passing we took all of the messages that
passing we took all of the messages that are coming from this factor to the
从这个因素到这个粒子集合的邻居
are coming from this factor to the neighbors of this particle collective
neighbors of this particle collective not to this node L and so one of those
而不是到这个节点L，所以这些消息之一进入您与
not to this node L and so one of those message is coming in you multiply with
message is coming in you multiply with of J and then you integrate all of the
的J，然后您将L以外的所有变量进行积分，这将为您提供
of J and then you integrate all of the variables except L and that gives you
variables except L and that gives you the update of the F of T pile and it
T桩的F的更新以及预期传播带来了
the update of the F of T pile and it comes with expectation propagation gives
comes with expectation propagation gives you exactly same answer okay if you
如果您不相信我留下的笔记，您的答案完全相同，但是我们
you exactly same answer okay if you don't believe me leave the notes but we
don't believe me leave the notes but we will come back on this on Thursday to
将于周四回到此查看期待的奇迹
will come back on this on Thursday to see the miracles of expectation
see the miracles of expectation propagation
传播